let history_question = [
    {
        question:"Philippines is made up of how many island?",
        choices:{
            a:"7,641",
            b:"8,200",
            c:"8,122"
        },
        answer:'7,641'
    },
    {
        question:"Philippines National Flower?",
        choices:{
            a:"Gumamela",
            b:"Sampaguita",
            c:"Santan"
        },
        answer:'Sampaguita'
    },
    {
        question:"How Many Active Volcanoes Philippines have?",
        choices:{
            a:"24",
            b:"64",
            c:"200"
        },
        answer:'24'
    },
    {
        question:"Smallest Province in the Philippines?",
        choices:{
            a:"Manila",
            b:"Batanes",
            c:"Ilo ilo"
        },
        answer:'Batanes'
    },
    {
        question:"Largest Province in the Philippines?",
        choices:{
            a:"Bulacan",
            b:"Davao",
            c:"Palawan"
        },
        answer:'Palawan'
    },
    {
        question:"Queen City of the South?",
        choices:{
            a:"Bacolod",
            b:"Davao",
            c:"Cebu"
        },
        answer:'Cebu'
    },
    {
        question:"9th Most largets Malls in the World?",
        choices:{
            a:"Mall of Asia",
            b:"Robinson Otis",
            c:"Sm City North Edsa"
        },
        answer:'Sm City North Edsa'
    },
    {
        question:"City Hall that shaped like a coffin?",
        choices:{
            a:"Imus City Hall",
            b:"Manila City Hall",
            c:"San Pedro City Hall"
        },
        answer:'Manila City Hall'
    },
    {
        question:"Rizal Park or Luneta Park also known as?",
        choices:{
            a:"Dating Bayan",
            b:"Bagumbayan",
            c:"Urban Park"
        },
        answer:'Bagumbayan'
    },
    {
        question:"Philippine National Animal?",
        choices:{
            a:"Philippine Eagle",
            b:"Tilapia",
            c:"Carabao"
        },
        answer:'Carabao'
    },
    {
        question:"Philippine National Bird?",
        choices:{
            a:"Maya maya",
            b:"Owl",
            c:"Philippine Eagle"
        },
        answer:'Philippine Eagle'
    },
    {
        question:"Spain ruled the Philippines for?",
        choices:{
            a:"Less than 2 years",
            b:"200 Years",
            c:"More than 300 Years"
        },
        answer:'More than 300 Years'
    },
    {
        question:"Considered as perfect perfect coned-shaped volcanoe.",
        choices:{
            a:"Mt. Pinatubo",
            b:"Mt. Mayon",
            c:"Mt. Isarog"
        },
        answer:'Mt. Mayon'
    },
    {
        question:"First National Hero of the Philippines?",
        choices:{
            a:"DR. Jose Rizal",
            b:"Andres Bonifacio",
            c:"Lapu-lapu"
        },
        answer:'Lapu-lapu'
    },
    {
        question:"Current National Hero of the Philippines?",
        choices:{
            a:"Emilio Jacinto",
            b:"Dr. Jose Rizal",
            c:"Emilio Aguinaldo"
        },
        answer:'Dr. Jose Rizal'
    },
    {
        question:"Founder of Revolutionary organization named KKK?",
        choices:{
            a:"Antonio Luna",
            b:"Apolinario Mabini",
            c:"Andres Bonifacio"
        },
        answer:'Andres Bonifacio'
    },
    {
        question:"Who Painted the Famous Spoliarium?",
        choices:{
            a:"Antonio Luna",
            b:"Graciano Lopez-Jaena",
            c:"Juan Luna"
        },
        answer:'Juan Luna'
    },
    {
        question:"Philippine National Hero called 'Hero of Tirad Pass'",
        choices:{
            a:"Marcelo Del Pilar",
            b:"Antonio Luna",
            c:"Gregorio Del Pilar"
        },
        answer:'Gregorio Del Pilar'
    },
    {
        question:"Founder of first Military Academy?",
        choices:{
            a:"Antonio Luna",
            b:"Jacinto Zamora",
            c:"Emilio Jacinto"
        },
        answer:'Antonio Luna'
    },
    {
        question:"Brain of Katipunan?",
        choices:{
            a:"Andres Bonifacio",
            b:"Emilio Jacinto",
            c:"Gregorio Del Pilar"
        },
        answer:'Emilio Jacinto'
    },
  ]
